Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Lingusitics, Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Linguistics, honors theses
1997-2007
SC4-4272
Stanford University. Department of Linguistics.
0.5 Linear feet (14 volumes in 1 box)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Dept. of Linguistics.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Information about Access
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Dept. of Linguistics.
Access Terms
Linguistics--Study and teaching.; Student papers.
Collection Contents
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Andrada, Cheryl Padua, Changing language and changing attitudes: the use of English kinship terms in an Ilocano community., 2002 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Rebecca Anne, The perception of foreign-accented speech by native and foreign speakers., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Geren, Joy Celeste, Parental cues in word learning: deictic terms and locational questions., 2002 (Box 1)
  - Theberge, Christine, About some sixth-grade rappers, writers, and readers., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Wallenberg, Joel Constine, The story of American self: a case study in morphological variation., 2003 (Box 1)
  - Yu, Jennifer, He Re'o O Ta'a Poki Nei E Rangi Atu Ena: language shift of Rapanui., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Chi, Yoo-Jean, When Seoul translates Hollywood: the use of Korean honorifics to encode pragmatic meaning in film subtitles., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Galati, Alexia, The representation of motion in language and gesture: a comparison of Greek and English., 2002 (Box 1)
  - Law, Franzo II, Is it justified to absolutely avoid splitting an infinitive? A diachronic analysis of the split infinitive., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Nakamura, Juno, Subordinate clauses in narrative fiction found in EFL texts used by Japanese high schools and ESL texts used in American high schools., 2000 (Box 1)
  - McArthur, Andrea, The SV/VS alternation in modern Hebrew children's literature., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Jabari Ali, El Español de los Negros del Norte de Esmeraldas, Ecuador (ENNEE)., 1997 (Box 1)
  - Delson, Rudolph, Fiction and disbelief., 1997 (Box 1)
  - Callier, Patrick, A corpus study of sentence-final me: "Cosmopolitan" Mandarin?., 2007 (Box 1)